{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Theater Accessory \u0026 Projector Installation Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46390/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46390,"taskName":"Home Theater Accessory - Install","taskDescription":"Install Home Theater Accessory","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Theater Accessory \u0026 Projector Installation Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":129,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Theater DVD CD projectors Playstation","textMessagingName":"Access Inst","rolloverLongDesc":"Installs Home Theater Accessories.  Components installed include Xbox, Playstation, DVD Player, CD Players and other electrical equipment.","rolloverShortDesc":"Installs Home Theater Accessories","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Home Theater Accessory.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Theater Accessory \u0026 Projector Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Accessories","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Install Home Theater Accessory","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Home Theater Accessory - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Theater Project","urlName":"Home-Theater-Accessory-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Theater Component \u0026 Projector Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Theater,DVD,CD,projectors,Playstation,Xbox,Displays,changers,Players,accessories","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1307,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46390/":{"taskOID":46390,"originalTaskOID":46390,"setID":1307,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6396,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8685,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new component","answerDisplayText":"Install new component","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8686,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing component","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing component","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6397,"questionDisplayText":"Component to install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What would you like to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8687,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"CD or Audio Player","answerDisplayText":"CD or Audio Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8688,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8689,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8690,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Xbox or Playstation","answerDisplayText":"Xbox or Playstation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Speakers","answerDisplayText":"Speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8692,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","answerDisplayText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8693,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Receiver","answerDisplayText":"Receiver","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6398,"questionDisplayText":"Cabling or concealment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you need cabling or wire concealment services?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8694,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8695,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6396,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8685,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new component","answerDisplayText":"Install new component","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8686,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing component","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing component","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8685,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new component","answerDisplayText":"Install new component","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8686,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace existing component","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing component","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6397,"questionDisplayText":"Component to install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What would you like to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8687,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"CD or Audio Player","answerDisplayText":"CD or Audio Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8688,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8689,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8690,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Xbox or Playstation","answerDisplayText":"Xbox or Playstation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Speakers","answerDisplayText":"Speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8692,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","answerDisplayText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8693,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Receiver","answerDisplayText":"Receiver","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8687,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"CD or Audio Player","answerDisplayText":"CD or Audio Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8688,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8689,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8690,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Xbox or Playstation","answerDisplayText":"Xbox or Playstation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Speakers","answerDisplayText":"Speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8692,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","answerDisplayText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8693,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Receiver","answerDisplayText":"Receiver","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6398,"questionDisplayText":"Cabling or concealment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you need cabling or wire concealment services?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8694,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8695,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8694,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8695,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}